School administration, parents and
students,
thank you for the long wait.
First of all, why is our helmet
important? Let's
end it in a short way. A life should not be lost due to a neck injury.
It should not be an accident.
It should not be the driver's error
or the accident perpetrator's error. We should do
our
research and punish everything. We should punish those who are not using it. It is because of
whom we punish and who is not using it that the
insurance company and the court should get
involved in this. You should come up with
some scheme, do
something. But life should not be
lost. You should increase the penalty section a
lot for that. Or you should increase the awareness.
But a life should not be lost for a trivial reason. Every year,
our  We have
taken statistics and
compared this year with last year,
we have reduced the number of deaths in Chennai City Police by one fifth in 2023 compared to 2022. It should be
much lower in 2023 than in 2022.
But what we are facing is that the number of vehicles in 2023 is higher
than the number in
2022,
but the infrastructure we have is the
same. So, if
we all drive without accidents and make this balance, we
can reduce these accidents.
The effort taken by this administration and this insurance company to save lives is so great in this
audio.  You have seen that no
one should give us unnecessary
advice to anyone, and similarly, no one should disturb our life unnecessarily.
These terms
and conditions of road safety helmet
awareness are for this reason. If you
follow this daily, we will reduce the number of lives lost by this queja. It is
unfair. No life
comes and goes carelessly. It comes and this is
an opportunity.
Everyone who drives a two-wheeler
should not drive without a helmet. If you follow it daily,
we can avoid unnecessary lives lost. We can be the reason for
creating a healthy society.
So, thank you very much to the
police for giving this opportunity and for getting involved in this.
Thank you very much to all the technicians.